BARBARA SATORI

A professional and communicative loan officer with six years of experience working in fast-paced commercial finance settings. Seeking to apply my skills to help LoanPlus become a market leader and provide innovative financing solutions. Regularly exceeded sales goals by 10 to 20 percent in previous roles while maintaining positive client relationships.

4714 Twin Oaks Drive, Grand Rapids, MI 49503 satorifi n a nce@e m a i l.com (555)000-5555

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COMMERCIAL LOAN OFFICER

Premier Financing, Grand Rapids, MI January 2018-Present

- Complete loan contracts, process loan applications, and counsel clients on policies and restrictions
- Interview customers to assess their needs and suggest different types of commercial loans that fit their goals
- ♦ Collect and analyze client financial information to assess loan eligibility

LOAN OFFICER

EZ LOAN, Grand Rapids, MI February 2016 - December 2017

- Originated Jumbo home loans ranging from \$750,000 to \$1,500,000
- Greatly extended the company's portfolio by bringing in over 100 new clients
- Met and surpassed company benchmarks with regards to credit quality, sales, and profitability

ASSOCIATE BANKER

Redwood Bank, Detroit, MI August 2015 - January 2016

- Provided exceptional customer service and educated clients on banking products and services
- Assisted customers with banking transactions, including deposits, withdraws, and wire transfers
- Promoted banking products like credit cards and investment accounts to existing banking customers

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business University Of Michigan Ann Arbor, MI September 2011 - May 2015

KEY SKILLS

- ♦ Financial Analysis
- ♦ Commercial Loan Processing
- ◆ Customer Satisfaction
- ◆ Communication
- ♦ Leadership

CERTIFICATIONS

Certifi cate i n Bu s i ness and
Commercial Lending, American
Banking Association, 2018